Personal Profile:

I am currently training to become a Full Stack Web Developer. Previously, I spent 16 years working in the Greetings Card Publishing industry, where I worked as a Proofreader and Repro Tech Checker, saving the company thousands of pounds a year in potential reprint costs. I am methodical and loyal with a good eye for detail.

Key Skills:

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Python 3
- Microsoft Office suite of programs
- Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator and InDesign
- AutoCAD
- Citrix databases

Experience:

Proofreader & Repro Tech Checker - UK Greetings, Corby 2011 - 2016

- Proofread Greetings Cards, Calendars and Diaries
- Checked digital integrity of production files
- Made corrections to files using Adobe Illustrator/Photoshop
- Ensured jobs matched specifications using Citrix database
- Released digital files to printers using DropSend
- Assisted Artworkers during busy periods

File Release Co-ordinator - Watermark Publishing, Corby 2004 - 2011

- Created Imposition sheets of Greetings Cards ready to be forwarded to UK printers
- Proofread and digitally checked PDFs
- Burned finished files to disc/released using an internet file transfer system

Transport Co-ordinator - Watermark Publishing, Corby 2000 - 2004

- Organised deliveries of work-in-progress Greetings Cards between various UK printers and card finishing suppliers
- Processed export orders and arranged for their delivery
- Visually checked imposition sheets created in the repro department

Architectural Assistant - Gelder & Kitchen, Corby 1999 - 2000

- Prepared architectural drawings using a CAD system
- Carried out site surveys
- Maintained the Health and Safety database

Project Assistant - Sara Lee Professional, Corby

1997 - 1999

- Surveyed factory buildings and prepared detailed project drawings
- Prepared the Daily Efficiency and Downtime reports
- Issued KPI information to the Management Accountant
- Designed new databases and spreadsheets for various departments

Training Courses:

- HTML Fundamentals Certificate
- CSS Fundamentals Certificate
- JavaScript Tutorial Certificate
- Python 3 Tutorial Certificate
- Creative Computing using Quark Xpress
- CAMIT Database Certificate
- Microsoft Excel Intermediate Certificate
- AutoCAD Introduction Certificate
- BTEC National Certificate in Building Studies
- CPVE in Engineering

Education:

Henry Gotch School, Kettering

•	Mathematics	GCSE
•	English Language	GCSE
•	Design	GCSE
•	Integrated Science	GCSE
•	Art	GCSE
•	Social Studies	GCSE
•	French	GCSE